adventurebox.com 2017-06-09

# Policy - Adventure Box

### Policy

Last updated: April 22, 2015

Adventure Box and the website are owned by the Swedish company Happy L-Lord AB. Happy L-Lord AB will collect personal data for the purpose of creating an account for you and in order to make Adventure Box better, faster, and more convenient for you. The data we collect are mainly your name and your e-mail address. We will also collect data about your visit to, and choices on, the website by using Cookies (small text files that temporarily will be stored on your computer). If you do not want us to store Cookies on your computer, you can change the settings on your browser, but this might make the website faulty.

We might use your personal data to send you information and offers about our products. We will also share it with our billing provider to make payments possible. We will typically not disclose your personal data to a third party without your explicit consent. However, we may be obliged to share some of your personal data in some situations, for example with tax authorities, if they request it, or in case our company is acquired by another company.

Think carefully about what you post in for example a forum at the website since this information is public and can be used by others.

The data we collect are stored on servers outside of Sweden. We follow the rules set by US-EU Safe Harbor Framework and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework, created by the US Department of Commerce regarding collecting, using and storing information from the EU, EES and Switzerland. You can read more about the Safe Harbor-program at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

You have the right to access all data we have about you. Contact us if you want this information. If any data is incorrect, incomplete or irrelevant you have the right to have this data corrected or removed. Your also have the right to ask us to stop any use of your data.

As Adventure Box and the website evolve, this Privacy Policy is likely to evolve with it. We will not reduce your rights under this policy without your explicit consent. We will post any policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a prominent notice.

Any privacy concerns should be directed to info@adventurebox.com; we take all privacy concerns very seriously and will respond appropriately and quickly.

_**CONTACT INFO**_

Last updated: April 12, 2015

Happy L-Lord AB (556963-6599)

Brännkyrkagatan 71

118 23 Stockholm

Sweden

CEO, Christopher Kingdon

Tel: +46 73 051 1414

Email: [info@adventurebox.com](mailto:info@adventurebox.com)
